Guide to the Clara Fraser Papers
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
Clara Fraser papers
1905-1998
University of Washington Libraries Special Collections Box 352900 Seattle, WA 98195-2900
3187
Fraser, Clara,$d1923-1998
23.3 cubic feet 27 boxes plus 1 sound cassette
Materials relating to a Seattle labor activist, including records of her suit against Seattle City Light and an oral history
Organized into 3 accessions.
Accession No. 3187-002, Clara Fraser papers, 1905-1983
Accession No. 3187-003, Clara Fraser papers, 1923-1998
Accession No. 3187-004, Clara Fraser papers, 1991-1997
Clara Fraser was born Clara Doris Goodman in Los Angeles on March 12, 1923 to Russian-Jewish immigrant parents, Samuel and Emma Goodman. Her father was an anarchist and her mother worked in the garment industry. She grew up in a multi-racial neighborhood, the East Side ghetto of Los Angeles, which Fraser described as a very poor, but highly political environment. While in junior high school in the 1930s, Clara joined the Young People’s Socialist League, prompted by the despair of the Great Depression. In 1939 to 1945, Fraser attended UCLA and graduated with degrees in literature, education, and drama. She then joined the Trotskyist Socialist Workers Party in 1945. After marrying at the age of 18, she and her first husband, Frank Krasnowsky, moved to Chicago. They then moved to Seattle to organize a Socialist Workers Party during the post-war era. Working as an assembly line electrician at Boeing, Fraser participated in the Boeing Strike of 1948. During the 1950s and 1960s, Fraser was very active in labor socialist politics. She worked vigorously to end racial segregation and the Vietnam War. She also supported women’s rights. In 1966 when the Seattle branch of the Socialist Workers Party left the organization, Fraser helped form the Freedom Socialist Party. Fraser and other feminists began a Free University of Seattle class titled "Marx and the Women's Question" which was the beginning of the Women's Studies Program at the University of Washington. Soon after, she joined the original Seattle Opportunities Industrialization Center (SOIC) and CEP, the job training arms of the anti-poverty program. She became a consultant on feminism and race relations for many public agencies. In 1967, Fraser, along with Gloria Martin and the young women of the New Left, founded Radical Women. Radical Women worked with and supported African American anti-poverty programs, Native American fishing rights, and Asian American protests for low-income housing.
After being fired from SOIC, Seattle City Light hired Fraser in 1973 as an education coordinator of the Electrical Trades Trainee Program for women. On July 11, 1975, Seattle City Light fired her, claiming that her dismissal was due to budgetary cuts. The Seattle Department of Human Rights, directed under Vivian L. Caver, a black woman civil rights and political activist, found that Fraser was discriminated because of her public affiliation with the Feminist Coordinating Council, Radical Women, and the Freedom Socialist Party. When the workers of Seattle City Light rose up against Superintendent Gordon Vickery, director of the agency, in 1974, Fraser was the leading critic and spokesperson for the massive employee walkout. She then became involved with a recall campaign against Mayor Wes Uhlman.
A legendary case not only in Seattle but across the nation, Fraser garnered broad support from local and national labor, feminist, gay, and labor unions, women’s groups, the LGBT community, and minority groups including the Black Panther Party chapters in Los Angeles and Seattle, the Native American Rights Advocate, and the Asian Law Association. In 1981, the court ruled in favor of Fraser, upholding protection for employees against sex and political discrimination. Seattle City Light was ordered to award her $135,265.00 in back pay, damages, and interests, reinstatement of her retirement account, social security contributions, and restoration of sick leave, dental and vacation benefits.
Fraser died on February 24, 1998 in Seattle, Washington.
Materials include correspondence, newsletters, press releases, and newspaper articles relating to the activities surrounding the lawsuit Clara Fraser vs. City Light and an oral history interview with Fraser by Charlotte McAllister (1970). Also included are pamphlets and booklets regarding radicalism, industrial unionism, anarchism, anarcho-syndicalism, Marxism, socialism, feminism, anti-war efforts, and anti-capitalism collected by Fraser (1905-1949). Personal papers include educational records; family memorabilia; calendars and diaries; and correspondence, as well as materials about cultural events that illustrate Fraser's wide range of interests.
Listen to the audio recording of this interview on the Libraries Digital Collections site.
No restrictions on access for paper-based materials. No user access copy is currently available for sound and video cassettes. Users may obtain a reproduction of the media for a fee by contacting Special Collections.
An additional interview with Clara Fraser can be found in the
Gary Greaves Seattle History Interviews, Manuscript Collection 5815
Megan Cornish papers (6259)
George Hammer papers (6276)
Communist Party of the United States of America; Industrial Workers of the World; Socialist Workers Party; Seattle City Light; International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 77; Labor movement$zUnited States; Labor movement$zWashington (State)$zSeattle; Labor union members$zWashington (State)$zSeattle; Labor union unions$zWashington (State)$zSeattle; Labor union$zWashington (State)$zSeattle; Radicalism; Socialist parties$zUnited States; Political parties$zUnited States; Newsletters; Personal Papers/Corporate Records; Labor History; Labor Unions; Civic Activism; Women; Washington (State); Seattle; California; Sound Recordings
- Clara Fraser papers, 1905-1983; 3187-002; 0.77 cubic feet 3 boxes plus 1 sound cassette
  Materials include correspondence, newsletters, press releases, and newspaper articles relating to the activities surrounding the lawsuit Clara Fraser vs. City Light and an oral history interview with Fraser by Charlotte McAllister (1970). Also included are pamphlets and booklets regarding radicalism, industrial unionism, anarchism, anarcho-syndicalism, Marxism, socialism, feminism, anti-war efforts, and anti-capitalism collected by Fraser (1905-1949).
  No restrictions on access.
  Radical pamphlets: Gift of Mr. and Mrs. Fraser, 1964; Clara Fraser Defense Committee materials received from the Committee: 6/81 and 4/86; Tape-recorded interview gift of Clara Fraser, 1995
  Arranged in 3 series.
  Series 1, Clara Fraser vs City Light
  Series 2, Collection of radicalist pamphlets
  Series 3, Interview with Clara Fraser
  - Clara Fraser vs City Light, Series 1
    - Progressive Mothers' League, 1954 (Box-folder 1/1)
      Four short articles concerning the political and economic position of women
    - Clippings, 1972-1981 (Box-folder 1/2)
      Articles about gender discrimination, Clara Fraser, and the City Light case
    - News Releases, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 1/3)
      United Feminist Front, Clara Fraser Defense Committee
    - "Clara Fraser vs. Seattle City Light" Newsletters, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 1/4)
    - TV Editorial by Don McGaffin, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 1/5)
      Regarding Clara Fraser vs. Seattle City Light
    - Statements of Support, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 1/6)
      Gay Community Center, Dr. Katherine Grant-Bourne, National Lawyers Guild, Seattle Tenant's Union
    - Correspondence, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 1/7)
      Melba Windoffer, Clara Fraser Defense Committee
    - Memos, phone lists, & proposed resolutions, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 1/8)
    - Event Handbills, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 1/9)
    - Clippings, 1980 (Box-folder 1/10)
      Clara Fraser and discrimination
    - Clippings, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 1/11)
      The Freedom Socialist, Beacon Hill News, Seattle Gay News, The New Portland Observer, The Asian Family Affair
    - Ephemera - Labor Issues, 1945-1958 (Box-folder 1/12)
    - Ephemera, 1956-1964 (Box-folder 1/13)
      Washington State black employment, United Liberals & Socialist Party, Freedom Socialist Party, Young Socialist Alliance, Communist Party of Washington
  - Collection of radicalist pamphlets, Series 2
    - Socialism, Subseries 1
      - "Wage-Labor and Capital" by Karl Marx, 1899 (Box-folder 2/1)
      - "Morals and Socialism" by Charles H. Kerr, 1899 (Box-folder 2/2)
      - "Socialists in French Municipalities" by Charles H. Kerr, undated (Box-folder 2/3)
      - "Socialism's New Beginnings" by Miles, 1934 (Box-folder 2/4)
      - "English Methods of Birth Control" by Margaret Sanger, 1915 (Box-folder 2/5)
      - "Socialism vs. Single Tax", 1906 (Box-folder 2/6)
      - "The Kingdom of Heaven is at Hand" by C.W. Woolridge, MD, undated (Box-folder 2/7)
      - "The Truth About Father Coughlin" by A.B. Magil, 1935 (Box-folder 2/8)
      - "Draft for a Program for the Socialist Party of the United States, 1935 (Box-folder 2/9)
      - "Problems of Revolutionary Socialism" by Haim Kantorovitch, 1936 (Box-folder 2/10)
      - "Letter of an Old Bolshevik", 1937 (Box-folder 2/11)
      - "Comrades and Friends" by Margaret Sanger, 1915 (Box-folder 2/12)
      - "The Twelves and You" by Elizabeth Gurley Flynn, 1948 (Box-folder 2/13)
      - "Inside Job!" by Herb Tank, 1947 (Box-folder 2/14)
      - "How to Win the Masses" by John Henry Baldwin, 1944 (Box-folder 2/15)
      - "Lenin on Relations Between Socialist States" by Milovan Djilas, 1949 (Box-folder 2/16)
      - "On People's Democracy in Yugoslavia" by Edward Kardelj, 1949 (Box-folder 2/17)
    - Industrial Unionism, Subseries 2
      - "By-Laws of the Construction Workers Industrial Union no. 573", 1919 (Box-folder 2/18)
      - "The Burning Question of Trades Unionism" by Daniel DeLeon, undated (Box-folder 2/19)
      - "Industrial Relations Commission" by Fred D. Warren, 1915 (Box-folder 2/20)
      - "Bats in the Belfry" by William Gropper, undated (Box-folder 2/21)
      - "Communist Election Platform", 1932 (Box-folder 2/22)
      - "How One Big Union Works: An Australian Example" by A.D. Dodds, undated (Box-folder 2/23)
      - "The Dictatorship of the Profiteering Class" by Henry M. Tischenor, undated (Box-folder 2/24)
      - "Has Religion Been a Promoter of Retarder of Civilization?" by Rosa Markus, 1915 (Box-folder 2/25)
      - "Industrial Conspiracies" by Clarence S. Darrow, 1912 (Box-folder 2/26)
      - "Set the 12 Men Free" by Henry E. Boote, undated (Box-folder 2/27)
      - "Socialist Industrial Unionism: The Worker's Power" by Eric Hass, 1943-1946 (Box-folder 2/28)
      - "The Crimes of the 'Times'" by Upton Sinclair, undated (Box-folder 2/29)
      - "Labor Fights for Social Security", 1935 (Box-folder 2/30)
      - "The Social General Strike" by Arnold Roller, 1905 (Box-folder 3/1)
      - "The Slander of the Toilers" by George R. Kirkpatrick, 1919 (Box-folder 3/2)
      - "The Advancing Proletariat" by Abner E. Woodruff, 1919 (Box-folder 3/3)
      - "The Dictatorship of the Proletariat" by L. Kameneff, undated (Box-folder 3/4)
      - "Communist Election Platform", 1938 (Box-folder 3/5)
      - "Union-Smashing in Sacramento" by Herbert Solow, 1935 (Box-folder 3/6)
      - "Industrial Unionism and Revolution" by Philip Kurinsky, undated (Box-folder 3/7)
      - "Should the Workers Increase Output?" by W.F. Watson, 1920 (Box-folder 3/8)
      - "The Social and Economic Lies of Our Civilization" by T. Swann Harding, undated (Box-folder 3/9)
      - "ABC of Parliamentary Law" by August Claessens and Rebecca E. Jarvis, 1936 (Box-folder 3/10)
    - Washington Labor, Subseries 3
      - "Vote NO on the Smash-the-Union Movement in Washington", 1938 (Box-folder 3/11)
      - "A Fair Trial?: A record of the prejudice and passion that dominated the legal profession and the press in the famous Centralia labor case" by Frank Walkin, 1920 (Box-folder 3/12)
      - "The Siamese Twins - Profits and Poverty", undated (Box-folder 3/13)
    - Industrial Workers of the World, Subseries 4
      - "Industrial Unionism and the IWW" by Vincent St. John, undated (Box-folder 3/14)
      - "Evolution of American Agriculture" by Abner E. Woodruff, 1919 (Box-folder 3/15)
      - "The Advancing Proletariat" by Abner E. Woodruff, 1919 (Box-folder 3/16)
      - "Proletarian and Petit-Bourgeois" by Austin Lewis, approximately 1912-1914 (Box-folder 3/17)
      - "The IWW: Its History, Structure, and Methods" by Vincent St. John, 1919 (Box-folder 3/18)
    - Anti-War, Subseries 5
      - "Stopping a War" by Scott Nearing, 1926 (Box-folder 3/19)
      - "Political Report of the Central Committee of the CPY [Communist Party of Yugoslavia]" by Josip Broz Tito, 1948 (Box-folder 3/20)
      - "Youth Fights War!" by Gus Tyler, undated (Box-folder 3/21)
      - "Are You Ready for War?" by Hal Draper, undated (Box-folder 3/22)
      - "Against Both War Camps" by Victor Howard, 1948 (Box-folder 3/23)
    - Socialist Literature, Subseries 6
      - "Now and Then: A Play in Two Acts" by Frederick Krafft, 1901 (Box-folder 3/24)
      - The Plutocrat" by George L. Ayere, undated (Box-folder 3/25)
      - "The Scarlet Review: Collection of Revolutionary Material Worth Reprinting," an IWW publication, The Equity Printing Company, Seattle, Washington, approximately 1918-1919 (Box-folder 3/26)
      - "Castaways of Plenty" by Willard E. Hawkins, 1945 (Box-folder 3/27)
  - Interview with Clara Fraser, Series 3
    - Tape-recorded interview with Clara Fraser by Charlotte McAllister, January 1970 (Cassette Drawer 1, Tape 27)
      Fraser states that Marx and Engels first described the black struggle in terms of the Civil War as a struggle of two classes and types of social organization. They looked on the war as a second "American Revolution." The IWW and Socialist Party first notices the black struggle shortly after 1900 when Booker T. Washington was their leader. She continues to discuss the different views towards blacks by the Socialists and Communists.
      Listen to the audio recording of this interview on the Libraries Digital Collections site.
- Clara Fraser papers, 1923-1998; 3187-003; 20.61 cubic feet 22 boxes
  Personal papers include educational records; family memorabilia; calendars and diaries; and correspondence, as well as materials about cultural events that illustrate Fraser's wide range of interests.
  Fraser's writings include articles she wrote for the Freedom Socialist newspaper, including a regular column. Records of speeches and educational talks include speaking notes, texts of speeches, and audiotapes and videotapes of selected speeches. Job records (1954-1973) include employment records and details of consulting work Fraser did before starting work at Seattle City Light. Publicity records include press coverage Freedom Socialist Party and Radical Women activities, of Fraser's political activities and activities at Seattle City Light, as well as interview transcripts and audiotapes.
  Clara Fraser's job as education coordinator at Seattle City Light was eliminated in 1975, and she filed a complaint with the Seattle Human Rights Department claiming discrimination based on sex and political ideology. She eventually won reinstatement with back pay in 1982. Records related to the case include: pleadings, filings and decisions related to the case before the City's Hearing Examiner; hearing transcripts; audiotapes of hearing proceedings; and exhibits. (Note: volumes 13-15 and volume 25 of the 43 volumes of hearing transcripts, representing 4 days proceedings, are missing from the record.) Additionally, the records includes pleadings, filings and decisions of King County Superior Court, which heard an appeal of the hearing panel's initial denial of Fraser's discrimination claim. Other related case records include case administration records, including fundraising files; records of case publicity; records of the related Electrical Trades Trainees' case; and extensive records of Seattle City Light activities and issues in the 1970s and 1980s. Clara Fraser's activities and City Light are documented in correspondence and document files from her first stint at City Light, and also in a series of correspondence from her return to City Light in 1982 until her retirement in 1986.
  Papers donated by Helen Gilbert of Radical Women and Freedom Sociliast Party, Seattle.
  No restrictions on access for paper-based materials. No user access copy is currently available for sound and video cassettes. Users may obtain a reproduction of the media for a fee by contacting Special Collections.
  Arranged in 15 series.
  Series 1, Personal Papers
  Series 2, Family Memorabilia
  Series 3, Calendars and Diaries
  Series 4, Correspondence
  Series 5, Publicity and Press Files
  Series 6, Writings
  Series 7, Speeches and Educational Programs
  Series 8, Subject Files
  Series 9, Travel and Retreat Records
  Series 10, Job Records
  Series 11, Consulting Job Records
  Series 12, Clara Fraser vs. Seattle City Light Employment Discrimination Case Records
  Series 13, City Light Background Files
  Series 14, Fraser Job Records while at City Light
  Series 15, Fraser job correspondence after return to City Light
  - Personal Papers, 1931-1998; Series 1
    - Certificates and diplomas, 1931-1944 (Box-folder 1/1)
    - School report cards, 1930-1938 (Box-folder 1/2)
    - Autograph books, 1933-1940 (Box-folder 1/3)
    - Papers for high school classes, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 1/4)
    - Note cards for paper on women in journalism, English 1A, 1939 (Box-folder 1/5)
    - Papers for college classes, 1941 (Box-folder 1/6)
    - Papers for college classes, 1942 (Box-folder 1/7)
    - Papers for college classes, 1943 (Box-folder 1/8)
    - Papers for college classes, Approximately 1938-1945 (Box-folder 1/9)
    - Writings: short story, Approximately 1938-1945 (Box-folder 1/10)
    - Divorce case, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 1/11)
    - Family memorabilia, 1978, 1995 (Box-folder 1/12)
    - Frank Krasnowsky, 1943, c. 1980s (Box-folder 1/13)
    - Dick Fraser memorial and obituaries, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 1/14)
    - Marc Krasnowsky: awards, 1970 (Box-folder 1/15)
    - Jon Fraser: Jazz Lab, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 1/16)
    - Jon Fraser, 1976-1985 (Box-folder 1/17)
    - Drawings and portraits, approximately 1955-1975 (Box-folder 1/18)
    - Photographs, 1923-1994 (Box-folder 1/19)
    - Good quotes, approximately 1970-1985 (Box-folder 1/20)
    - Marxism study notes, 1953 (Box-folder 1/21)
    - Spanish class, 1988 (Box-folder 1/22)
    - In defense of materialism class, 1954 (Box-folder 1/23)
    - Origins of the family, 1950 (Box-folder 1/24)
    - The Victory of socialism in one country and the defeat of the left opposition, approximately 1950-1970 (Box-folder 1/25)
    - Chart of political line of the Third International, approximately 1950-1960 (Box-folder 1/26)
    - Stalinism and Comintern information, approximately 1950-1960 (Box-folder 1/27)
    - Notes on economics, approximately 1950-1960 (Box-folder 1/28)
    - Note on the black question, approximately 1950-1970 (Box-folder 1/29)
    - Words/notes, approximately 1990-1998 (Box-folder 1/30)
    - Biographical sketches, 1980-1996 (Box-folder 1/31)
    - Resumes, 1980-1996 (Box-folder 1/32)
    - Book blurbs, 1996 (Box-folder 1/33)
    - Tributes to and roasts of Clara, 1982-1996 (Box-folder 1/34)
    - Clara 70th birthday & welcome Jonnie Fraser 3/21/93, 1993; VHS video cassette (Box-folder 18/7)
    - Happy birthday Clara from Portland branch, 1994; VHS video cassette (Box-folder 18/8)
    - International Women's Day march / Happy birthday Clara from New York branch, 1994; VHS video cassette (Box-folder 18/9)
    - Clara - happy birthday '94 (Seattle tape), 1994; VHS video cassette (Box-folder 18/10)
    - Birthday greetings Clara Fraser from Bay Area branch, 1994; VHS video cassette (Box-folder 18/11)
    - Telephone poles; Dinner & Barbeque - by Flory Adler, Approximately 1980s; VHS video cassette (Box-folder 19/4)
    - Tacoma for Clara, Approximately 1990s; VHS video cassette (Box-folder 19/5)
    - Revolution she wrote: video draft 2/12/98, 1998; VHS video cassette (Box-folder 19/6)
    - Play script -- Coffee, cigarettes and class, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 1/35)
    - Play script -- Coffee, cigarettes and class, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 1/36)
    - Clara Fraser photographs, Approximately 1980s (Box-folder 1/37)
    - Arts, culture, entertainment souvenirs, 1961-1982 (Box-folder 1/38)
    - Playbills and music programs, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 17/19)
    - Playbills and music programs (part 1 of 2), 1985-1986 (Box-folder 17/20)
    - Playbills and music programs (part 2 of 2), 1985-1986 (Box-folder 17/21)
    - Humor, 1978-1981 (Box-folder 1/39)
  - Family Memorabilia, 1969-1997; Series 2
    - Jonny memorabilia, 1971-1978 (Box-folder 1/40)
    - Jon Fraser solo piano concert 1/1/97 (2 copies), 1997; VHS video cassette (Box-folder 19/7)
    - Marc Krasnowsky articles, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 1/41)
    - Marc Krasnowsky articles (part 1 of 2), 1985-1992 (Box-folder 1/42)
    - Marc Krasnowsky articles (part 2 of 2), 1985-1992 (Box-folder 1/43)
    - Marc Krasnowsky articles, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 1/44)
    - Marc Krasnowsky articles, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 1/45)
    - Marc Krasnowsky articles, 1994 (Box-folder 1/46)
  - Calendars and Diaries, Series 3
    - Diary, 1936 (Box-folder 1/47)
    - Datebook, 1978 (Box-folder 1/48)
    - Work calendar, 1974 (Box-folder 2/1)
    - House calendar, 1973 (Box-folder 2/2)
    - House calendar, 1975 (Box-folder 2/3)
    - House calendar, 1977 (Box-folder 2/4)
    - House calendar, 1983 (Box-folder 2/5)
    - Bedroom calendars, 1983, 1986, 1992 (Box-folder 2/6)
    - Address cards, approximately 1970-1980 (Box-folder 2/7)
    - Address books (part 1 of 2), approximately 1960-1990 (Box-folder 2/8)
    - Address books (part 2 of 2), approximately 1960-1990 (Box-folder 2/9)
  - Correspondence, 1950-1996; Series 4
    - Emma Goodman (mother), 1950-1959 (Box-folder 2/10)
    - Emma Goodman (mother), 1960-1969 (Box-folder 2/11)
    - Emma Goodman (mother), 1970-1979 (Box-folder 2/12)
    - Dick Fraser, 1967-1978 (Box-folder 2/13)
    - Marc Krasnowsky, 1973-1989 (Box-folder 2/14)
    - Jon Fraser, 1971-1994; Leather-bound volume (Box-folder 2/15)
    - Adler family, 1976-1994 (Box-folder 2/16)
    - Raya Fidel, 1989-1996 (Box-folder 2/17)
    - Correspondence: general, friends and family, 1963-1994 (Box-folder 2/18)
    - Birthday and holiday cards, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 2/19)
    - Birthday and holiday cards, 1983 (Box-folder 2/20)
    - Birthday party, 1993 (Box-folder 3/1)
    - Birthday cards, 1993 (Box-folder 3/2)
    - Cards and thank-yous, 1993 (Box-folder 3/3)
  - Publicity and Press Files, 1969-1998; Series 5
    - List of press clippings on Clara Fraser, 1969-1979 (Box-folder 3/4)
    - Publicity and press coverage, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 3/5)
    - Publicity and press coverage, 1971 (Box-folder 3/6)
    - Publicity and press coverage, 1972 (Box-folder 3/7)
    - Publicity and press coverage, 1973 (Box-folder 3/8)
    - Publicity and press coverage, 1974 (Box-folder 3/9)
    - Publicity and press coverage, 1975 (Box-folder 3/10)
    - Publicity and press coverage, 1976 (Box-folder 3/11)
    - Publicity and press coverage, 1977 (Box-folder 3/12)
    - Publicity and press coverage, 1978 (Box-folder 3/13)
    - Fraser case press coverage, 1979 (Box-folder 3/14)
    - Fraser case press coverage, 1980 (Box-folder 3/15)
    - Fraser case press coverage, 1981 (Box-folder 3/16)
    - Fraser case press coverage, 1982 (Box-folder 3/17)
    - Fraser case press coverage, 1983 (Box-folder 3/18)
    - Fraser case press coverage, 1984 (Box-folder 3/19)
    - Fraser case press coverage, 1985 (Box-folder 3/20)